Her safety. His mission.
Shelter is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Ric Roman Waugh.
Mason lives in recluse at a remote setting by the sea.
When he chooses to rescue a young girl from drowning in a terrible storm, he unwittingly sets off a chain
reaction that soon brings violence his way, forcing him to confront choices from his past.
Michael Mason, played by Jason Statham.
Jesse, played by Bodhi Rae Breathnach.
Shelter is a 2026 action thriller film directed by Ric
Roman Waugh and written by Ward Parry.
It stars Jason Statham, Bodhi Rae Breathnach, Bill
Nighy, Naomi Ackie, and Daniel Mays.
Shelter premiered at the Cineworld Leicester Square in London on January 20, 2026, and is
scheduled to be released in the United States on January 30, by Black Bear Pictures.
The tone is intense.